Guide to the Kingsley Memorial Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- JAMES LUCE KINGSLEY PAPERS, 1803-1852; Series I; 2' (5 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Kingsley, James Luce
      - Perit, Mrs. Maria, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - Perit, Pelatian, 1823, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - Savage, James, 1848-1852 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Sparks, Jared, 1829-1851 (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - Thompson, Benjamin F., 1829, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Kingsley, Jonathan, 1815, 1846 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Kingsley, Lydia (Coit) (Box 2, Folder 82)
      See also:box 1, folder 65
    - Kingsley, Martin, 1836 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Kingsley, Phinehas, 1840-1841 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Kirkland, John T., 1825 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Knight, Martha K., 1828, 1836, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Lane, Ebenezer, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Larned, William Augustus, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Livermore, George, 1849 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Ludlow, Henry Gilbert, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Middlebury College, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Mills, Elijah Hunt, 1828 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Morse, Richard Carey, 1826 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Morse Samuel Finley Breese, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - New York Literary and Philosophical Society, 1815 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - North, Simeon, 1835 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Noyes, Joseph, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Olmsted, Denison, 1819, 1822, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Palfrey, John Gorham, 1824-1839 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Park, Edwards Amasa, 1852 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Perit, Pelatian, 1833, 1842, 1843 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Perkins, George, 1840 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Perkins, Simon, 1841 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Phaedros, Kyriacus G., 1827, 1828, undated (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Pierce, John, 1847 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Ralli, Constantine Theodore and Stephen J. Gallati, 1831 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Rhode Island Historical Society, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Robbins, Royal, 1826 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Rockwell, John Arnold, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Salisbury, Edward Elbridge, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Savage, James, 1848-1852 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Shelton, Helen King, 1806, undated (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Silliman, Benjamin, 1804-1851 (Box 2, Folder 113-114)
    - Sparks, Jared, 1826-1851 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Stedman, James, 1835 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Stevens, Henry, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Stoddard, David. J., 1849 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Stoddard, Solomon, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Storrs, Henry Randolph, 1828 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Stuart, Moses, 1830 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Taylor, Zachary, 1844 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1844, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Thayer, Sylvanus, 1826 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Tolland County Bank, 1839 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Tracy, ____, 1849 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Turner, Samuel Hulbeart, undated (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Twining, Stephen, undated (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Walsh, Robert, 1819, 1845 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Webb, Thomas Hopkins, 1835 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Wilcox, Phineas Bacon, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Willard, Emma (Hart), 1852 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Willard, Sidney, 1809, 1832, 1833 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Wolcott, Frederick, 1835 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Wood, S., 1845, 1848 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight, 1825, 1845, 1846 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Worcester, Jonathan Fox, 1851 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Worcester, Joseph Emerson, 1803-1852 (Box 3, Folder 136-140)
    - Yale College Class of 1821, 1851 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Unidentified, 1834 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Personal papers
    General note
    See also: box 14, folders 649-651
    - Account books, 1812-1852 (Box 4, Folder 142-146)
      See also: box 17, folder 759
    - Award, 1828 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Essays, 1814, undated (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Grade book, 1847-1848 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Report, 1828 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Lectures
      - History, undated (Box 5, Folder 151-152)
      - Language, undated (Box 5, Folder 153-154)
      - "On George P. Marsh's Phi Beta Kappa discourse at Harvard, 1847", undated (Box 5, Folder 155)
      - Roman law, 1815 (Box 5, Folder 156)
      - Miscellanea, undated (Box 5, Folder 157)
- WILLIAM L. KINGSLEY PAPERS, 1830-1898; Series II; 2.5' (6 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Abbot, Ezra, 1864, 1865 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Abbot, Nelly W., 1868 (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - Adams, George Burton, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - Aikman, Robert, Jr., 1845-1893 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - Allen, Walter, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - Alpha Delta Phi Society, 1845, 1851 (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - American Tract Society, 1846 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - Anderson, Rufus, 1864 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - Andrews, W. W., 1862-1866 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - Appleton, D., and Company, 1867 (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - Armitage, William E., 1862 (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - Atterbury, Albert H., 1889, 1892 (Box 6, Folder 169)
    - Atterbury, Charles L., 1866 (Box 6, Folder 170)
      See also: box 6, folder 196
    - Atterbury, Edward J. C., 1882 (Box 6, Folder 171)
    - Atterbury, John G., 1862 (Box 6, Folder 172)
    - Atterbury, William Wallace, 1844-1895, undated (Box 6, Folder 173-176)
    - Atwater, L. H., 1864 (Box 6, Folder 177)
    - Atwater, Wyllys, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - Atwood, Charles K., 1893 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - Atwood, G. H., 1866, 1869 (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - Avery, John, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 181)
    - Bacon, Elizabeth R., 1864 (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - Bacon, Francis, 1891 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - Bacon, Leonard W., 1866, 1866 (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - Bacon, Theodore, 1879 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - Badger, Milton, 1863 (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - Baldwin, George W., 1890 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - Bancroft, George, 1862 (Box 6, Folder 188)
    - Barnard, Henry, 1856, 1857 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - No folder (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Bates, George Timothy, 1855 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - Bates, Loulie, undated (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - Bates, Morris Upham, 1871, 1890, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - Belden, Herbert C., 1863 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - Benton, Joseph Augustine, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Betts, Atterbury, Hyde and Betts, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - Blackburn and Brooking, 1856 (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - Blake, Elizabeth Coit (Kingsley), 1837-1890 (Box 6, Folder 198)
      See also: box 8, folder 360
    - Blake, Henry Taylor, 1860-1862, undated (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - Blake, Isabel, 1875 (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - Blakeslee, Samuel Valentine, 1847 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - Blood, Daniel Cole, 1840, 1854 (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - Bourne, Henry E., 1889 (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - Bouton, George, 1852 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - Bowne, Borden Parker, 1873-1876 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - Brace, S. C., 1891, 1892 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Braley, Stephen, 1877 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - Brewster, James, 1861 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - Brewster, Joseph, 1870 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - Bristed, Charles A., undated (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - Brooks, Phillips, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - Brush, George Jarvis, 1872 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Buckingham, S. G., 1894 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - Buckingham, William A., 1865, 1872 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Bumpus, Edward A., undated (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Burgess, Ebenezer, 1864 (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Bushnell, Horace, 1863 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Chamberlain, Daniel H., 1876-1893 (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - Chapin, Fanny L., 1892 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Chapman, Susannah, undated (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - Chauncey, Nathaniel, 1863 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Christopher, J. W., 1889 (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - Citizens' Law and Order League, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Clark, George H., 1892, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Clark, H. K., 1869 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Clarke, I. Edwards, 1877-1883 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - Coe, E. B., [1867?] (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - Coffin, Mrs. S. H. W., 1863 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Coit, Charles W., 1895 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - Coit, Daniel L., 1830, 1832 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Coit, Daniel W., 1860-1869 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - Coit, William H., 1895 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - Collins, C. T., 1867 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - Collins, Mary C., 1892 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - Cook, Albert S., 1891, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - Cooper, Jacob, 1862 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - Coxe, Bishop Arthur Cleveland, 1848, 1874 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - Crane, Edward B., 1861 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - Crosby, Howard, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Curry, J. L. M., 1888 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Daggett, Mary, 1891 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Daggett, O. E., 1870 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Dale, James W., 1867 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Dana, Henrietta (Silliman), 1864 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Dana, James Dwight, 1844, 1869 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Davies, L. Sanford, 1889, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Day, George E., 1863, undated (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Day, Horace, 1864 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Dechert, Edward Porter, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - DeForest, Henry Swift, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Depew, Chauncey M., 1890 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - DeStyrap, H. G. Jukes, [1853?] (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Dexter, Franklin B., 1886, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Dexter, Henry Martyn, 1880, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Downes, William E., 1891 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Dulles, John W., 1860, 1862 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Durrie, William A., 1893 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - Dwight, Timothy, 1868-1895 (Box 7, Folder 258)
      See also: box 10, folder 519
    - Eames, Benjamin T., 1892, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - Eaton, Daniel Cady, 1872, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - Edwards, Alfred L., 1893 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Eells, Edward, 1893, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - Ely, Charles, 1861, 1864, 1865 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - Ely, G. H., 1869 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - Emery, Samuel Hopkins, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - Everett, Edward, 1863 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - Fanning, Joshua, 1850 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Farnam, Elizabeth, 1871, 1876, undated (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Farnam, Henry W., 1895 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Finney, Charles Grandison, 1863, 1869 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Fisher, G. P., 1855, 1886 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - Folwell, William Watts, 1870 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Ford, Emily E., undated (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - Fowler, W. C., 1863 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - Freeman, Edward A., 1888, 1889 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - Gelston, Mills B., 1893 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - Gibbs, Josiah Willard, II, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Gillett, E. H., 1869 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1853-1895 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - Gilman, Edward Whiting, 1839-1895, undated (Box 7, Folder 280-281)
    - Gilman, Eliza Coit, 1846-1860 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Gilman, Emily Serena, 1856, undated (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Gilman, Julia (Silliman), 1850 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Gilman, Katherine Beecher (Perkins), 1854 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Gilman, Maria Perit, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Gilman, Mary (Ketchum), 1864 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Gilman, William Charles and Company, 1862 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Gilman, William Charles, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Gilman, William Charles, Jr., 1861-1886 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Goodhue and Company, 1855 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Goodrich, Chauncey, 1865 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - Goodrich, William Henry, 1839-1874 (Box 7, Folder 293-294)
    - Goodwin, Henry Martyn, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Grant, Frank Kingsley, 1896 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - Greeley, Horace, 1856 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - Greene, Gardiner, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Greene, George Washington, 1867 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Gulliver, John Putnam, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Haines, Elizabeth C., 1889 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Hall, G., 1852 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - Hanna, John Smedes, 1862 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - Harper, W. R., 1888 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Harris, Samuel, 1870 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - Hart, Burdett, 1888, 1889 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Hoskins, David Greene, Jr., 1895 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Hayden, Frederick Smith, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Head, John Frazier, undated (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Heaton, Isaac E., 1890 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Higgs, William, 1894 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Hine, Sylvester, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Hoadly, Charles Jeremy, 1870, 1890 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Holst, Hermann Eduard von, 1870 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Holt, Charles, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - Holt, Henry and Company, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Hoppin, James Mason, [1888?] (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Hosmer, James Kendall, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - Hotchkiss, Bertha, 1890 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Hotchkiss, Henry L., 1888 (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - Hotchkiss, Justus Street, 1886, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - Hoyt, A. H., 1888 (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - Hoyt, James E., 1851, 1852 (Box 8, Folder 323)
    - Hubbard, Oliver Paysan, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 324)
    - Hubbard, William B., 1892 (Box 8, Folder 325)
    - Hubbell, Peter, 1862 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - Humphrey, Edward Porter, 1868 (Box 8, Folder 327)
    - Hunt, Lucy T., 1894, undated (Box 8, Folder 328)
    - Hurlbutt, Lewis Raymond, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - Ives, Nathan Beers, 1866 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - Jackson, Mary C., undated (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - Jay, John, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - Jenckes, Thomas Allen, 1870 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - Jennings, William Jessup, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - Johnson, Samuel William, 1892 (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - Johnston, Alexander, 1889 (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - Johnston, Henry Phelps, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - Kappa Delta Society, 1838 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - Kellogg, Louise A., 1893 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - Kellogg, Sanford Brown, 1891, 1892 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - Kelsall, W. S., 1853 (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - Kelsey, Francis Willey, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - Kingsbury, Frederick John, 1888 (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - Kingsley, Charles, 1850, undated (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - Kingsley, George Theodore, 1833-1841 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - Kingsley, H. Louise (Upham), 1857-1868, undated (Box 8, Folder 346-351)
    - Kingsley, Henry Coit, 1833-1875, undated (Box 8, Folder 352-357)
    - Kingsley, J. S., 1887, undated (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Kingsley, [Jacob?], 1857 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - Kingsley, James Luce, 1840-1848 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Kingsley, Lydia (Coit), 1842-1855 (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - Kingsley, Maurice, 1891 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Kingsley, Rose G., 1874, undated (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Kingsley, V. W., 1885 (Box 8, Folder 364)
    - Kingsley, Walter G., 1883 (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - Kingsley, William Lathrop
      - Blake, Elizabeth Coit (Kingsley), 1848, 1852, 1853 (Box 8, Folder 366)
        See also: box 9, folder 373
      - Dana, James Dwight, 1844 (Box 8, Folder 367)
      - Farnam, Henry
        See: box 12, folder 589
      - Farnam, Henry Walcott, 1878-1886 (Box 8, Folder 368)
      - Gilman Daniel Coit, 1855-1890, undated (Box 9, Folder 369-370)
      - Gilman, Edward Whiting, 1839-1874 (Box 9, Folder 371-372)
      - Kingsley, Elizabeth Coit, 1835 (Box 9, Folder 373)
      - Kingsley, George, 1832, 1842 (Box 9, Folder 374)
      - Kingsley, H. Louise (Upham), 1857, 1859 (Box 9, Folder 375)
      - Kingsley, Henry Coit, 1835, 1848 (Box 9, Folder 376)
      - Kingsley, Henry Coit and Jane (Thomas) Handy Kingsley, 1848 (Box 9, Folder 377)
      - Kingsley, James Luce, 1848 (Box 9, Folder 378)
      - Kingsley, Lydia (Coit), 1833-1855 (Box 9, Folder 379)
      - "Yale Book": prospectus, 1876 (Box 9, Folder 380)
      - Miscellanea, 1859-1890, undated (Box 9, Folder 381)
    - Kirk, Edward Norris, 1866 (Box 9, Folder 382)
    - Kyle, Emilie H., 1854 (Box 9, Folder 383)
    - Lane, Harriet Lathrop (Gilman), 1861, undated (Box 9, Folder 384)
    - Learned, Dwight Whitney, 1884 (Box 9, Folder 385)
    - Learned, James Edgerton, 1889, 1890 (Box 9, Folder 386)
    - Learned, Robert Coit, 1866 (Box 9, Folder 387)
    - Leavitt, Joshua, 1863 (Box 9, Folder 388)
    - Lieber, Francis, 1868 (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - Livermore, Russell Wolcott, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 390)
    - Lord, John, undated (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Lucas, George Clark, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - MacVeagh, Wayne, 1890, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - McCook, Willis Fisher, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - McLaughlin, Edward Tompkins, undated (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - McWhorter, Alexander, 1864 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Magoun, George Frederick, 1865, 1867 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Mansfield, George S., 1869 (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - Mason, Louis B., 1894 (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - Massie, James William, 1868 (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - Maze, John, 1882 (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - Meech, George Appleton, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Merritt, I. J., 1854 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Metcalf, David, 1863 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Mitchell, Donald Grant, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Moore, George Henry, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - Morris, William Bowen, 1860 (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Mundé, Charles, 1866-1873 (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Mundé, Paul Fortunatus, 1863, 1872, 1873 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - Mundy, E. F., 1868 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Munger, Theodore Thornton, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Munson, Frederick, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - Needham, Edgar, 1865 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Nevins, William
      See: box 15, folder 685
    - Newton, Hubert Anson, 1869 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - North, James Hamilton, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 415)
    - Norton, Elizabeth E., 1874 (Box 9, Folder 416)
    - Nott, Samuel, 1857-1893 (Box 9, Folder 417)
    - Osborn, Norris Galpin, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 418)
    - Padelford, Marion, 1854 (Box 9, Folder 419)
    - Palfrey, John Gorham, 1862, 1871 (Box 9, Folder 420)
    - Palmer, Charles Ray, 1890 (Box 9, Folder 421)
    - Palmer, J., 1854 (Box 9, Folder 422)
    - Park, Edwards Amasa, 1864 (Box 9, Folder 423)
    - Parker, Mary Ann (Bissell) Coit, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 424)
    - Patterson, Robert William, 1868, 1869 (Box 9, Folder 425)
    - Peabody, Andrew Preston, 1862-1892 (Box 9, Folder 426)
    - Peck, William Stedman
      See: box 15, folder 687
    - Perit, Maria Coit, 1862-1888, undated (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - Perit, Pelatiah, 1841 (Box 9, Folder 428)
    - Perkins, Frederick Beecher, 1859 (Box 9, Folder 429)
    - Peters, Absalom, 1863 (Box 9, Folder 430)
    - Phillips, Andrew Wheeler, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 431)
    - Phillips, Wendell, 1862 (Box 9, Folder 432)
    - Pierce, George Taber, 1893, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 433)
    - Porter, John Addison, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 434)
    - Porter, Josephine Earle (Sheffield), 1868 (Box 9, Folder 435)
    - Porter, Mary (Taylor), undated (Box 9, Folder 436)
    - Porter, Noah, 1870-1874 (Box 9, Folder 437)
    - Porter, Samuel, 1876 (Box 9, Folder 438)
    - Potwin, Thomas Stoughton, undated (Box 9, Folder 439)
    - Prichard, M., 1863 (Box 9, Folder 440)
    - Prime, Wendell, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 441)
    - Rhode Island Historical Society, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 442)
    - Richardson, Charles Francis, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 443)
    - Ripley, Hannah Gardiner (Lathrop), 1861 (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - Robbins, Edward Wright, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Rogers, John Sill, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 446)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1890 (Box 9, Folder 447)
    - Russell, John Edward, [1888?] (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - Russell, William Huntington, undated (Box 9, Folder 449)
    - Salisbury, Edward Elbridge, 1862, undated (Box 9, Folder 450)
    - Sands, John Drozier, 1847, undated (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - Sargent, Joseph Bradford, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 452)
    - Satterlee, Henry G., 1888 (Box 9, Folder 453)
    - Schaff, Philip, 1861, 1863 (Box 9, Folder 454)
    - Scudder, Horace Elisha, 1882 (Box 10, Folder 455)
    - Sewall, John Smith, 1890, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 456)
    - Shields, Charles Woodruff, 1868 (Box 10, Folder 457)
    - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr., 1865 (Box 10, Folder 458)
    - Silliman, ____, undated (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - Silliman, Susan Huldah (Forbes), undated (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Smith, Burritt Augustus, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - Smith, Katharine Wadsworth (Bacon), undated (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - Stanton, Robert Palmer, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - Starbuck, C. C., 1888 (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - Stedman, Edward Clarence, 1865, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - Stevens, Henry, 1845-1871 (Box 10, Folder 466)
    - Stimson and Atterbury boys, 1882 (Box 10, Folder 467)
    - Storrs, Richard Salter, 1863, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 468)
    - Stowe, Calvin Ellis, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - Strong, William, 1888 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - Sturtevant, Julian Monson, 1868 (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - Sweetser, Moses Forster, undated (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - Tarbox, Increase Niles, 1879, 1888 (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - Terry, Alfred Howe, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Thacher, Thomas, 1886 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1856, 1878, undated (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - Thompson, Elizabeth Coit (Gilman), 1847-1891, undated (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - Thompson, John H., 1860 (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - Thompson, Joseph Parrish, 1852-1863 (Box 10, Folder 479)
    - Thompson, William Gilman and Company, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - Titcomb, Philip, 1845 (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - Townsend, Amos, 1862 (Box 10, Folder 482)
    - Townsend, Howard, 1856 (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - Trapier, William Heyward, 1856 (Box 10, Folder 484)
    - Trumbull, Henry Clay, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 485)
    - Trumbull, James K., 1888 (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - Turner, Douglas Kellogg, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - Tuttle, George F., 1883 (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - Twichell, Joseph Hopkins, undated (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - Upham, Nathaniel Lord, 1862 (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - Upson, Henry, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Waddington, John, 1866, 1872, 1873 (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Waite, Morrison Remick, 1886 (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Walker, George Leon, 1882 (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Walker, Joseph Burbeen, 1870, 1895 (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Warner, George Welton, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Watson, Helen F., 1866, 1867 (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Wayland, Heman Lincoln, 1864 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Weaver, William L., 1860 (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Webster, Noah, 1834, 1842, undated (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - Weeks, Robert Kelley, 1871 (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - White, James T. and Company, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Whitney, William Dwight, undated (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - Wickes, John, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Wickham, Joseph Dresser, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Wight, Orlando Williams, 1888 (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Wilcox, Marrion, 1885 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Winn, John, 1868 (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Winthrop, Robert Charles, 1871, 1879 (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - Wise, William G., 1863 (Box 10, Folder 510)
    - Wolcott, C. M., 1871 (Box 10, Folder 511)
    - Wood, George Ingersoll, undated (Box 10, Folder 512)
    - Woolsey, Theodore Dwight, 1867-1889, undated (Box 10, Folder 513)
    - Worcester, Joseph Emerson, 1860 (Box 10, Folder 514)
    - Wright, Henry Parks, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 515)
    - Yale College Board of Examiners, 1839 (Box 10, Folder 516)
    - Young, Mason, 1885 (Box 10, Folder 517)
    - Condolence letters, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 518-519)
  - Personal papers
    See also: box 14, folders 666-667
    - Account books
      - Personal, 1848-1888 (Box 11, Folder 520-527)
      - Division Street Church, [1861?]-1874 (Box 11, Folder 528)
      - New Englander and Yale Review, 1886-1889 (Box 11, Folder 529)
    - Diary, 1843-1854 (Box 11, Folder 530)